So for today's video I have help here from Laura. Hi! Nice to be here because we're going to show you the new restraint system from Strict Senses.
Yes! You're already playing with it the whole time. Yes. It's a really innovative magnetic lock system and you can walk to the camera and show it.
So you just take this magnet and you open it and you just put it on top and it's closed. Like you can't open it anymore.
and this is a gray set but we also have other colors we're going to show it to you in red in
a second with a nice red catsuit oh yes but we don't only have the arm pieces but also like the
whole set do you want to like unpack it yes i feel like christmas okay so i think this is for
my thighs maybe? Is it? It could be yeah the size is... This too? Okay so we picked this one out it's for the arm
okay so let me close this so just put it through here
and here through so just place it on top now it's all closed nice so it's really tight it's really
fast like you don't need a lot of time to close it and just put it on top again
and it's open again I think it's really handy because yes it's like I love it
already the system itself is called SeguFix it's a human restraint and
positioning system and it's basically the lock of the whole PVC straps and
and brings everything together, it's really sturdy.
So I couldn't open it without the key.
And also when it's closed, I think barely can,
I don't know, you can't take it off.
And with the PVC, it's really tight.
And you would definitely not get out of it without my help.
But with my help it works.
I know where I've seen it.
Oh, you do?
I've seen it in hospitals.
In hospitals?
Yeah, I've worked in hospitals some time ago
and they use it there.
So like it's a German product and it's really common.
I mean, it also has a TÜV certificate.
Yeah, which is really important for German people.
Which is really a German thing to like test everything
and give out like certificates.
We know the gray one,
but I got another Strix Senses system,
which you're going to try out.
It's red.
Nice.
And I have the matching catsuit here
because Strix Senses has a sister company
called Bright and Shiny.
Oh, I know this one already.
Yeah.
Yeah, we're already wearing bright and shiny
Because they make latex and spandex, but I think this is going to be a nice match
So it has gloves and feet
Cool and the hood
Whoo, so you have to change now. Okay, I will
You know the first time I saw this it wasn't really really nice picture from Six Senses where they paired this exact catsuit with these
restraints so I want to basically rebuild it because I love the pictures
they were so cool okay
Sometimes you're better off dead
There's a gun in your hand
That's pointing at your head
You think you're mad
Too unstable
Kicking in chairs
And knocking down tables
In a restaurant
In a western town
Call the police
There's a madman around
Running down
Underground
To a dive bar
In a western town
A dead end world
With the eastern boys
And western girls
In a western town
the dead end world the eastern boys and western girls nice i lost something okay yeah i mean
that's the downside of the pvc it's uh of the pvc on the spandex spandex is a bit slippery i think
it would stick more to latex or to skin looks already good we have the collar so you would
have to yeah i'll take off my steel and then we'll put up the yeah okay i'm a bit excited
I can give you the tip for the hood if you tilt your head backwards it's easier
okay well let's try well actually it's not that hard
I mean it's stretchy everything is stretchy
I'll close it there we go okay okay
you should be able to see like a bit of light yeah I see a light there and one
there but and you should be able to breathe yeah yeah I can breathe that's
really easy. That's fine. If something feels uncomfortable just tie it. That's fine.
A little bit of pressure on my nose but yeah it's better now.
It's not uncomfortable. You have to navigate me. Just stand like that.
Everything done and now I'm going to close them. Now I'm simply going to put all the
buttons basically on the restraints.
Okay, now that I've closed everything, do you feel okay turning around once?
I can hold your hand if you're afraid to fall.
Nice.
You're like a ballerina.
Looks really, really cool, awesome, and we also have restrained belts, so to say, which
I will put on two. And if you're wondering how to do it or what parts you need,
Strix Answers has a page on their homepage on which they list everything
you need to build these looks basically. And I will check the picture again too.
Okay so I'm going to attach your wrists to your tie. Now I have these separate
parts with the metal for the backside attached. I'm going to detach them like
this. I'm going to put the back side metal part from the back to the front and loop
everything through that and again close it. Done. Next slide. Here we go finally.
And lock it again. I have one last belt and I think this is for the arms so would you
mind turning around please? Thank you. So I'm going to loop it through your upper arm
restraints. Now. How tight can I? It's okay. Like I want to have a symmetry here. Go for
One, two, three, four. One, two, three, four, fifth. Like this.
And the last one.
There we go.
This is the complete look. I think it looks so good.
Can you turn around again?
So nice. I'm going to take off your hood in a second so you can see yourself.
But I think this looks so awesome.
Really really great. And it was so easy and fast and I think it looks really elegant.
And I also love the contrast with the black and red and silver.
Nice! How do you feel? Are you okay? Yeah, amazing.
It's really tight. You're so quiet!
Okay, pulling the hood off. Careful with the hair.
Okay. Hello!
Oh my god, let me fix it.
Nice!
Okay, it's really cool with the hood.
Cool.
Like this.
Actually, I didn't really see anything.
Only a bit of light and some movement, but breathing is easier than I thought.
So to everyone who claims that you can't really breathe when wearing a hood, you said you
could breathe fine.
So urban myth.
Breathing is fine.
This one was the hardest. Yeah? Yeah, because your posture is not used to stand like this all the time.
Like really squeezing the shoulder blades together. But the rest is really easy. But it looked really good.
Alright, you're free again. Yes. And we have something else because Strix Senses does not
only have the Zegofix closure, but classic lockable buckles. You wanna put this on me?
okay yes this is a belt yes that's the perfect place i think so okay if you want should the
the d-rings be in the middle i would say yes depends i would say the middle of the front
is more important on the back side then like okay okay nice okay if you would have like um
a lock now you could put it on put the chanel around it couldn't open it oh that looks cool
It's just nice like fashion accessory. It pins every outfit. Yeah it's just a really nice belt.
It's really cool.
It's a lot of metal. It's a lot of metal. Oh we also have other colors. We also have other colors.
Yeah like in this box. What's white? It is white and gold. Oh that would also look really cool
cool with your latex. Great but you can like show it to the camera again.
I also have a leash because I'm nice actually so we could attach oh my god
attach it to each other like that yeah looks awesome that's very good right yeah it's a really
bright contrast with red and white and gold yeah nice bit like Christmas
And apart from these we also got some more transparent straps which you can utilize in various ways.
They have the same lockable that your belt has too.
It's really long so you can use them to restrain someone on the bed for example.
Or like all around. Like many all around.
You could wrap us together!
We're not going to show this though.
Better not.
I was wondering why this is so long, but the uni-size.
So when you wrap this fits all.
I could wrap it around like this.
It's really fast as well.
And you don't have to lock it.
No, you don't have to.
I mean, it's closed like that.
You don't need locks for every strand.
So but enough of you being your spring in this video
Actually, you know, can you put them like on? Yeah, they will look so cool on the latex. My hand and I think oh
Yeah, I'm just thinking about
Okay, so is that okay? Yeah, that's fine. Oh
oh when you're wearing latex you have to make sure you have them at all oh it's too yeah because
it's too loose it's fine yeah it's just people can see it yeah the color combination is really
yeah that's really nice yeah i'm not the gold uh kind of girl but no yeah but i think i like gold
this combination white gold yeah yeah nice all right i think we're done for today yes got
everything like a lot of stuff a lot of really cool stuff still love the look
with the belt is really nice I think it's going to even if you don't use it
as a restraint it's just nice yeah the look is amazing it's just nice look yeah
anyway thanks for being here today thank you for helping me out thanks to
Strix senses and bright and shiny for sending the items along I hope you all
have fun leave a thumbs up and a comment and all the stuff you're supposed to do
on YouTube when you like the video I will link her socials down in the
description text of course so you can have a look at her Instagram and yeah
yeah I think it's a girl alright anyway have a nice day I think we'll have
something to eat now yes yeah and we'll see you or I see you in the next video
bye bye